short-hair-style.com 2019-06-14

# Short-Hair-Style.com - Privacy Statement

Short-Hair-Style.com respects your privacy and committed to provide you with a safe online experience. This Online Privacy Statement is made available to you in order to make you aware of how Short-Hair-Style.com collects and uses information of visitors to this website. 

### Traffic Data

Short-Hair-Style.com collects the following information regarding visitors to this Website: We collect traffic information like IP address, domain name, browser type, access times and referring Web site address and information regarding what pages are accessed. 

### Personal Data

Short-Hair-Style.com will NOT collect personal information from visitors other than what is supplied on a voluntary basis, such as survey information, competition entry, newsletter or entering confirmation e-mail address on our interactive community system. 

Short-Hair-Style.com will never sell, rent, trade, loan or disclose your personally identifiable information to outside parties. 

Short-Hair-Style.com sometimes team up with trusted third party companies to bring you special offers, gifts and other exciting services. Even In those cases Short-Hair-Style.com will never disclose your personally identifiable information without your permission. 

As a visitor and user, you are in control. If you sign-up for newsletter or used any facility that asked for your e-mail you can always unsubscribe at any time by clicking on "unsubscribe" links in each of our newsletters or emails or just simply by contacting us. If you join our community service, you have full control on your privacy through your profile settings. 

### External Links

Short-Hair-Style.com contain links to other sites. Although we review each link and the destination on a regular basis we do not accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. 

### Use Of Cookies

Your browser offers a service called "cookies" which in todays technological advances is used almost by any website you visit. If you allow their use in your browser, it will store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit our Web site. They do not contain any personally information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. These small data simply assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. 

Cookies additionally used by reputable advertisers on this website. Google Adsense use Cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. A web beacon is normally is a small single-pixel image that is used to count users who have visited a specific page on our website. These data are used to enhance visitors experience regarding the type of advertising served. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying settings in your browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site. If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you may use their opt-out tool... <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

### Third Party Advertising Vendors

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART/DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
  * Users can also "opt out" of the behavioral advertising delivered by some other member companies. [To opt out of an NAI member's behavioral advertising program](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

### Childern and Minor

Some of the sections of this website is visited by children under the age of 12 while looking for hairstyles and advice for their look. We are strongly committed to protec the safety and privacy of those children to this website. All our interactive community system are reviewed before approving any post to this website. We do not allow and remove any language, photos or images unsuitable for young children. **This is a family-safe website**. 

### Updates and Changes to Policy

Short-Hair-Style.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it. 

### Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to Short-Hair-Style.com's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. 

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please [contact us here](http://www.short-hair-style.com/contact.html).
